Guide to the Gay and Lesbian Pulp Fiction Collection 1955-1988 MSS 116 MSS.116
Fales Library and Special Collections
- First Accretion
  - Drive Shaft Library 111. Richards, Mark: Stud For Sale. (Arena Publications), 1982 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Drive Shaft Library 120. Taylor, Rick: Deep Load. (Arena Publications), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061131 4
  - Drive Shaft Library 126. Taylor, Rick: Cruising For A Three-Way. (Arena Publications), 1982 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Eldorado Editions 102. Ironstone, John: Gay Rights. (Maverick), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Ember Library 376. Davidson, Chris: Go Down, Aaron. (Greenleaf), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ember Library 381. Davidson, Chris: A Different Drum. (Greenleaf), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Ember Library 386. Holliday, Don: The Gay Days. (Greenleaf), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Empire Book 1007. Laurtec, Bernard: The Queen. (Zil Inc.), 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Encounter Book 106. Riggles, Jon: Country Cousin. [ Signed by Author.] (Encounter), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Encounter Book 107. Stephens, Mick: Danny Malone's Way: Adventures of a Tough Gay Detective. (Encounter), 1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Eros Goldstripe 101. Fremoni, J: Gay Blades. (Eros Publishing), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Eros Goldstripe 102. Lagusker, Irwin: Joy Sticks. (Eros Publishing), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Eros Goldstripe 103. White, S: Gay Times. (Eros Publishing), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Eros Goldstripe 104. Davis, Corey: Male Box. (Eros Publishing), 1973 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Eros Goldstripe 107. Wisher, Peter: Size Queen. (Eros Publishing), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Eros Goldstripe IGL-1. Case, Curry: Sixty Ninth Street Super. (Eros Publishing), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Eros Goldstripe IGL-2. Case, Curry: Hustling Hackie. (Eros Publishing), 1971 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Eros Goldstripe GGS-109. Keith, W: Meat Force. (Eros Publishing), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Europa Book 807. Hanson, Doris: Voyage to Lesbos. (L.S. Publishing), 1967 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Exotik Book W-10. Sarrow, Russ: The Gay Game. (Exotik Books), 1965 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Fabian Original Novel 103. Shane, Mark: That Lady Was A Man. (Fabian), 1955 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Fanfare Publications. Ramp, James H: The Love Smeller. (Fanfare), undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Fawcett Gold Medal P3074. Hurwood, Bernhardt, J: The Bisexuals. (Fawcett), 1974 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Finland Books 26. Anonymous: Whip Master. (Star Distributors), 1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - First Niter Books 110. Kosloff, Myron: Dial P For Pleasure. (Connoisseur Publications), 1964 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061132 2
  - French Line 15. Starr, Michael: Hollywood Homo. (Publisher's Export), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - French Line 21. Dunn, Mark: Queer Guise. (P.E.C.), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - French Line 22. Carter, Ben: Sixty Nine Gay Street. (P.E.C.), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - French Line 23. Driver, Carl: Gay Cruise. (P.E.C.), undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - French Line 29. Culver, Ed: Queer Hustler. (P.E.C.), 1967 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - French Line 35. Shrader, Bert: Homo, House of Male Order. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - French Line 37. Shrader, Bert: Fee Males. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - French Line 42. Shrader, Bert: Gay Tutor. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - French Line 43. Harper, James: Gay Brother. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - French Line 44. Evans, Daniel: Glory Hole. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - French Line 46. Austin, Drew: Queer Pen. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - French Line 49. Harper, James: Queer View of Ted. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - French Line 51. Roberts, Brad: The Greek Touch. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - French Line 52. Fox, Alan: Fickle and Gay. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - French Line 53. Harrington, Len: Pansy Paradise. (P.E.C.), 1968 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - French Line 54. Mathews, Dan: Slave Man. (P.E.C.), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - French Line 57. Harrington, Len: Gay Swap. (P.E.C.), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - French Line 63. Geis, Alex: Jailhouse Queen. (P.E.C.), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - French Line 84. Evans, Dale: Bitch Boy. (P.E.C.), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - French Line 87. Taylor, Don: The Pile Drivers. (P.E.C.), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - French Line 88. Corbett, Neville: Queer Fear. (P.E.C.), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - French Line 90. Royce, Roger: Gay Gang-Up. (P.E.C.), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - French Line 99. Ford, Christopher: Inside Out. (P.E.C.), 1971 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 12. Ahern, John: The Search. (Frenchy's), 1969 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 14. James, Allen: The Manager. (Frenchy's), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 15. Harnes, Peter: The Arms of Arum. (Frenchy's), 1970 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 16. Macnore, Nala: The Thief. (Frenchy's), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061133 0
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 17. Harnes, Peter: Snowbird. (Frenchy's), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 18. Roger: Love. (Frenchy's), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 21. Lamb, Sebastian: Come Naked To My Arms, Gentle Savage. (Frenchy's), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Frenchy's Gay Line 22. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Mirror Chronicles. (Frenchy's), 1971 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Gaslight Books 117. Hitt, Orrie: Male Lover. (L.S. Publications), 1964 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Gay Collection Series. Smith, Houston: J Way-The Only Way. (Publisher's Consultants), 1977 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Gay Incest 120. Anonymous: Bondage Boys. (Star Distributors), 1982 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Gay Incest 122. Anonymous: Brothers At Sea. (Star Distributors), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gay Incest 123. Anonymous: Backyard Twins. (Star Distributors), 1987 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Gay Incest 132. Anonymous: Tricking With Dad. (Star Distributors), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Gay Incest 134. Anonymous: Dad Made Me Do It. (Star Distributors), 1988 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Gay Novel 403. Dawson, Greg: The Butt Boy. (Greenleaf), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Gay Novel 414. Thomas, Aaron: Bitch Boy. (Greenleaf), 1973 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Gay Parisian Press. Butler, L: Gay Realization. (Gay Parisian Press), undated (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Gay Parisian Press 100. Butler, L: Trick Trip. (Gay Parisian Press), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Gay Parisian Press 104. Cochran, Bob: Young Wild and Sexy. (Gay Parisian Press), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Gay Parisian Press 105. Rome, Jerry: The Straight Go-Go Boy. (Gay Parisian Press), 1970 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Gay Power Line 101. Harlow, Sherwood: Soul Brothers. (F.S. Publishing), undated (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Gay Power Line 102. Barber, Sonny: Live One. (F.S. Publishing), undated (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Gay Power Line 103. Rogers, Dan: Troubled Lovers. (F.S. Publishing), undated (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Gay Power Line 104. Young, Karl: Where Eagles Pair. (F.S. Publishing), undated (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Gay Times Book Club 12. Anonymous: Raw Recruit. (Star Distributors), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Gay Times Book Club 13. Anonymous: Strapped. (Star Distributors), 1980 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Gay Times Books Club 83. Anonymous: Freshman Class Sissy. (Star Distributors), 1984 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Gay Way 107. Jones, Dick: Man Eater. (F.S. Publishing), undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061134 8
  - Gay Way 111. Wharton, Jim: Naked Cowboy. (Surrey House), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Gay Way 112. Young, Karl: Suddenly It's Speed. (F.S. Publishing), undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Gay Way 114. MacLain, Richard: City of Men. (XXX Inc.), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Gay Way 115. Powell, Brad: Shadow On the Sand. (XXX Inc.), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gay Way 116. Ford, Christopher: Christopher's Craft. (XXX Inc.), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Gay Way 118. Cochran, Bob: Desert Discovery. (XXX Inc.), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Gay Way 119. Ford, Christopher: Christopher's Phallusies. (XXX Inc.), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Gay Way 120. Frank, Jerry: He Whore. (XXX Inc.), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Gay Way 122. Park, Barry: Cut Loose-Pretty Boy. (XXX Inc.), 1971 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Gay Way 123. Cochran, Bob: Swim Meat. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Gay Way 125. Rogers, Lance: Comin' Thru The Y. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Gay Way 126. Ford, Christopher: 'Midst Pleasure and Phalluses. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Gay Way 127. Holst, Gorman: Man Rape. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Gay Way 128. Young, Karl: Guess Who's Up In the Loft?. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Gay Way 129. Kiva, George: Never Quite Alone. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Gay Way 130. Esbee, W: Prickly Heat. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Gay Way 131. Carter, Vic: Things Never Went Right... (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Gay Way 132. James, Jerry: Wyoming Station. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Gay Way 133. Bent, Williams: No Holds Barred. (XXX Inc.), undated (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Gay World Special. Fox, John: Blowing In theWind. (s.l.), undated (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Gay World Special. West, Hunter: The Greek Way. (s.l.), undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Gold Medal Books S976. Packer, Vin: The Girl On the Best Seller List. (Fawcett Publications), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061135 5
  - Gold Medal Books S1066. Bannon, Ann: The Marriage. (Fawcett Publications), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Golden Boy Books 115. Reich, Kyle: Macho Brother. (Arena Publications), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Golden Boy Books 118. Reich, Kyle: Night of the Animals. (Arena Publications), 1978 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Golden Boy Books 127. Tyler, Bryant: Shaft. (Arena Publications), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Greenleaf Classics 212. Lockwood, Tom: Sons of a Beach. (Greenleaf), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Greenleaf Classic 213. Amory, Richard: Song of the Loon. (Greenleaf), 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Greenleaf Classic 261. Barrows, Philip: Whores, Queers, and Others. (Greenleaf), 1967 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Greenleaf Classic 296. Kovar, Dallas: One to Share. (Greenleaf), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Greenleaf Classic 330. Paris, Orlando: The Short and Happy Sex Life of Stud Sorrell and Sixty-Nine Other Flights of Fancy. (Greenleaf), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Greenleaf Classics 351. Caulder, Thorpe: Headlines For Johnny and Other Stories. (Greenleaf), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Greenleaf Classic 352. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: The Other Party. (Greenleaf), 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Hardboy Series 119. Curtis, Brad: Locker Room Suckers. (Star Distributors), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Hardboy Series 123. Sharkey, Barry: Trucker's Boy. (Star Distributors), undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Hardboy Series 503. Anonymous: The Cadet Master. (Star Distributors), 1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Hardboy Series 1002. Harden, Rick: Hung Butt Baller. (Star Distributors), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Hardboy Series 1004. Towers, Peter: Cock Happy Crew. (Star Distributors), 1974 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Hardboy Series 1008. Ferren, George: Let My Boys Come. (Star Distributors), 1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Hillman Books 129. Ackworth, Robert C: The Moments Between. (Hillman), 1959 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 6902. Curtis, Frazer: Come In. (Surrey House), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 6903. Hart, Roger: Husbands and Lovers. (Surrey House), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - HIS '69. 6906. Cochran, Bob: Crotch Bait. (Surrey House), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - HIS '69. 6908. Dickerson, Vic: Hairport. (Surrey House), 1971 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - HIS '69. 6909. Cockran, Bob: Easy Come. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061136 3
  - HIS '69. 6911. Brunner, Ace: Highway Hustler. (Surrey House), 1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - HIS '69. 6913. Cockran, Bob: Backdoor Seller. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - HIS '69. 6915. Kevork, K: In Black In White. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - HIS '69. 6916. Cummings, Rich: Hotel Dick. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - HIS '69. 6921. Cummings, Rich: Dingling Daddy's Dong. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - HIS '69. 6923. Cockran, Bob: Cocksuckers. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - HIS '69. 6927. MacLean, Curt: Teenage 69. Memoirs. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - HIS '69. 6929. Herman, Chuck: Bike Boy. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - HIS '69. 6930. Griffon, David: Jocksucker. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - HIS '69. 6934. Caldwell, Clay: Truckin' Naked. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - HIS '69. 6935. Cummings, Rich: Lip Service. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 6936. Love, D.H.: Steam Room Stroker. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 6937. Cummings, Rich: Ten-Inch Toker. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 6938. Smith, Houston: Cell-Mating. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - HIS '69. 6840. Gibson, Daniel: Well Hung-Up. (Surrey House), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 6953. Cockran, Bob: Head Giver. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 6954. Adcock, Ron: Seventeen X Nine. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 6960. Cockran, Bob: Flood Cumin'. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 6961. Cruze, Abel: Ride A Long Horn. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 6963. Frank, Harry: Up Your Alley. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - HIS '69. 6972. Murphy, Jeff: Door-To-Door Chicken. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - HIS '69. 6975. Todd, Eric: Three-Way Plug-In. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - HIS '69. 6976. Jeffries, Frank: Deep Dick. (Surrey House), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - HIS '69. 6977. Masters, Jock: Get It In Gear. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061137 1
  - HIS '69. 6980. Cummings, Rich: Shoot It Out. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - HIS '69. 6982. Hart, Roger: Come For Lunch. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - HIS '69. 6989. Foxx, Warren: Plug-In Stud. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - HIS '69. 6991. McCandless, Chance: Rock Hard. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - HIS '69. 6992. Pepper, Pete: Prime Meat. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - HIS '69. 6997. Gilbert, Dan: All Dick. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - HIS '69. 69100. Stewart, Lon: Back Door Buddy. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - HIS '69. 69111. Wilson, George: Bare Butt Rider. (Surrey House), 1974 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - HIS '69. 69129. Stoner, Larry: The Hole Thing. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - HIS '69. 69139. Jennings, Newt: The Cops Are Comin'. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - HIS '69. 69140. West, Samuel: Down, Boy. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 69145. Thomas, Len: Hard-Ass Hardhat. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 69147. Caldwell, Clay: Tailpipe Trucker. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 69148. DiCarlo, Manny: Rigid and Ready. (Surrey House), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - HIS '69. 69149. Johnson, Thumper: Slapping Balls. (Surree LTD.), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 69150. Thomas, Len: Suck It, Slave. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 69151. Pepper, Peter: Big Dick. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 69152. West, Samuel: Blow Boy. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 69154. Michaels, Ward: Cocky Cruiser. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 69155. St. John, Larry: Bang the Boy. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - HIS '69. 69156. Pepper, Peter: In Tight Twins. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - HIS '69. 69157. MacLean, Curt: Teenage '69. Memoirs. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - HIS '69. 69158. Rowen, Stuart: Hung Straight. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - HIS '69. 69159. George: Franz: Tied Chicken. (Surree Limited), 1975 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - HIS '69. 69161. Thomas, Len: Hot, Hunky Cruiser. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061138 9
  - HIS '69. 69162. Michaels, Ward: Ream the Team. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - HIS '69. 69163. St. John, Larry: Prison Pluggers. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - HIS '69. 69164. Jennings, Newt: Coach's Big Rock. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - HIS '69. 69165. Pepper, Peter: Hot Butt Eager. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - HIS '69. 69166. Jennings, Lyle: Chicken Trainer. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - HIS '69. 69167. Johnson, Thumper: Cock-Eyed Cruiser. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - HIS '69. 69168. West, Samuel: Tricking the Chicken. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - HIS '69. 69169. Cochran, Bob: School Meat. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - HIS '69. 69170. Johnson, Thumper: Backfield Motion. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - HIS '69. 69171. Pepper, Peter: Hard Driver. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - HIS '69. 69172. West, Samuel: Chicken Trick. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 69173. St. John, Larry: Hard Plowin'. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 69175. Rowen, Stuart: First Time Chicken. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 69176. Murray, Gene: Gang-Bang Bikers. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - HIS '69. 69177. Charles, Saxby: Daddy's Chicken. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 69178. West, Samuel: Lickin' Lad. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 69179. Scott, Michaels: S and M Bike Slave. (Surree Limited), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 69180. Hancock, Bob: Truck Stop Hunk. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 69181. Gordon, Howard: Chicken Camp. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 69182. Rowen, Stuart: Break-In Boy. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - HIS '69. 69183. Jordan, Buck: T-Room Chicken. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - HIS '69. 69184. Hancock, Bob: Trucker Comin'. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061139 7
  - HIS '69. 69185. Kenton, Sam: Hard Man To Hold. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - HIS '69. 69186. Mordell, Daniel: Big Rod. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - HIS '69. 69187. Jacobs, Jimmy: Star Stud. (Surrey House), 1976 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - HIS '69. 69190. Scott, Michael: Training Buddies. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - HIS '69. 69193. Hunter, Dick: Chicken Trick. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - HIS '69. 69194. Scott, Michael: Big Stinger. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - HIS '69. 69195. Langley, David: California Creamin'. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - HIS '69. 69198. Scott, Michael: College Jocks. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - HIS '69. 69199. Michaels, Ward: Meat Man. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - HIS '69. 69200. Dennis, Marley: Teachin' The Chicken. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - HIS '69. 69202. Penn, Ronald: Hung Up Hunk. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 69201. Scott, Michael: Full Throat. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 69203. Stuart, Chad: Gusher Comin'. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 69204. Hancock, Bob: Boarded and Bound. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - HIS '69. 69205. Montague, Murray: Hardhat Fever. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 69207. Rose, Dustin: Fiery Fists. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 69208. Sage, Buck: Western Mouthful. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 69209. Jennings, Lyle: Young and Horny. (Surrey House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 69210. Scott, Michael: English Leather. (Surree LTD.), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 69211. Dick, John: Blue Stud. (Surree LTD.), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - HIS '69. 69212. Stroth, Dick: Wild Bar. (Surree House), 1977 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - HIS '69. 69213. Scott, Michael: Skin-Flick Studs. (Surree House), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061140 5
  - HIS '69. 69214. McBride, Scott: Hang 'Em Low. (Surree House), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - HIS '69. 69215. Stuart, Chad: Back Room Terror. (Surree House), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - HIS '69. 69217. Montgomery, Rex: Man-Made Stud. (Surree House), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - HIS '69. 69219. Lance, Roy: Hollywood Call Boy. (Surree House), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - HIS '69. 69220. Hardy, Tom: Leather Slaves. (Surree LTD.), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - HIS '69. 69221. Michaels, Ward: Farm Boys. (Surree LTD.), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - HIS '69. 69222. Scott, Michaels: Hard Hat Master. (Surree LTD.), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - HIS '69. 69223. Grand, Alex: Boot-Camp Trick. (Surree LTD.), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - HIS '69. 69224. West, Samuel: Trick Me Easy. (Surree LTD.), 1977 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - HIS '69. 69225. Garfield, Dick: Sea Sucker. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - HIS '69. 69226. Stroth, Dick: Young Hunk. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 69227. Stuart, Chad: Animal Man. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 69229. Smith, Robin G: My Sex Island. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 69230. Gronowski, Paul: Bizarre Triangle. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - HIS '69. 69231. Graeme, Roland: Hung Peter. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - HIS '69. 69233. Riggles, Jon: His Cycle Master. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - HIS '69. 69234. McClain, Burt: Bi-Sex Stand. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - HIS '69. 69235. LaFong, Lance: Locker Room. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - HIS '69. 69236. Savage, Lon: Hunky Trade. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - HIS '69. 69237. Bistroff, Ted: Massage Parlor Stud. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - HIS '69. 69238. Stroth, Dick: Studs For Sale. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - HIS '69. 69239. Samson, Roger: Dynamite Dick. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - HIS '69. 69240. Hughes, Peter Tuesday: Hard To Shoot. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    bar code #: 3 1142 04061141 3
  - HIS '69. 69241. Moore, Martin: Hot Cop's Buns. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - HIS '69. 69242. Gronowski, Paul: College Hunk. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - HIS '69. 69246. Michaels, Bob: Hunky Roommates. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - HIS '69. 69247. Graeme, Roland: Reform-School Punks. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - HIS '69. 69248. McBride, Scott: Lavender Triangle Murders. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - HIS '69. 69249. Ward, Mike: Tom's Big Pole. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - HIS '69. 69250. Caldwell, Clay: Camp Buddies. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - HIS '69. 69251. West, Samuel: All Day Sucker. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - HIS '69. 69253. McBride, Scott: Devil's Phallus. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - HIS '69. 69254. Langley, David: Hunky Hitchhiker. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - HIS '69. 69256. Bennett, P.H: Choice Beef. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - HIS '69. 69258. Caldwell, Clay: Service Stud. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - HIS '69. 69261. Gronowski, Paul: Dangerous Trade. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - HIS '69. 69262. West, Samuel: Turned-On Chicken. (Surree LTD.), 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)